niftytrader.in 2019-11-06

# Privacy Policy - Nifty Trader's Resources

Niftytrader.in is committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity and security of all personal information about our users. This Privacy Policy explains how we protect personal information provided through our website http://www.niftytrader.in/, (the “Site”) and how we use that information in connection with our service offered through the Site (the “Service”). “Personal information” for purposes of this Policy means information that identifies you, such as your email address or your mobile phone number.

**A. Disclosure, if required by law**  
If required by Government of India or similar Organizational bodies, niftytrader would be sharing your personal information to the extent being demanded.

**B. Your data is secure**  
We use a combination of encryption techniques and authentication procedures, among others, to maintain the security of your online session and to protect  Niftytrader.in/ accounts and systems from unauthorized access. When you register for the Service, Niftytrader requires a password from you for your privacy and security. Niftytrader transmits information such as your Registration Information for Niftytrader.in/ or Account Credentials securely.

Our databases are protected from general employee access both physically and logically. We encrypt your Service password so that your password cannot be recovered, even by us. All backup drives and tapes also are encrypted.

No employee may put any sensitive content on any insecure machine (i.e., nothing can be taken from the database and put on an insecure laptop).

**C. Confidentiality of your Login ID and Password**  
Your password must be atleast 6 characters in length. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your Login ID and Password. You may not provide these credentials to any third party. If you believe that they have been stolen or been made known to others, you must contact us immediately at care@niftytrader.in/ , but in any event you should change your password immediately via the Service.

**D. We do not disclose or sell email addresses or mobile numbers**

**The DoubleClick cookie**

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to Niftytrader website.
  * Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * If you have not opted out of third-party ad serving, the cookies of other third-party vendors or ad networks may also be used to serve ads on your site.
